http://bluebuddies.com/privacy/

2020 Smurfs Christmas Advent Calendar!
SMURF FORUM
Smurfs DVD  McDonald's Smurfs  Fan Art  Smurf Song  Smurfs Character Names  Cartoon Episode Guide
What is your Smurf Nickname?  Promo Smurf Figurines  Make a Smurf Costume  Smurfette  Send a Smurf Greeting Card
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
What is the BlueBuddies.com privacy policy? The answer can be found right here!
Questions and Answers:
What is our Privacy Policy and When Does it Come Into Effect?
Effective Date: January 1, 2005.The following Privacy Policy governs BlueBuddies.com's online information collection practices. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that BlueBuddies.com gathers about you while using the BlueBuddies.com website (the "Service"), and the ways in which BlueBuddies.com uses (and does not use) this information.Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting the BlueBuddies.com website, you agree that your use of our Service, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. BlueBuddies.com may need to change our Privacy Policy from time to time. In such case, we'll post the changes to our Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the BlueBuddies.com website after we post any such changes, you agree to accept the Privacy Policy as modified.
What Information is Collected About Our Visitors?The information that BlueBuddies.com collects about you while you are using the Service falls into two general categories:1. Information You Provide:BlueBuddies.com may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply while on the BlueBuddies.com website. Some examples of this type of information include your name, email address and demographic information that you electronically submit when you sign up for access to certain features on the Service, information that you post on message boards on the BlueBuddies.com website, and information contained in search requests or queries you submit to the BlueBuddies.com website. If you decline to supply or provide BlueBuddies.com with certain information while using the Service, you may not be able to use or participate in some or all of the features offered through the Service.2. Information Automatically Collected:BlueBuddies.com also collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you traverse the BlueBuddies.com website. For example, BlueBuddies.com uses a standard web browser feature called a "cookie", which are small text files placed on your hard drive by your web browser. By showing how and when visitors use the BlueBuddies.com site, cookies help us detail user trends and patterns. Cookies also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences and personal information on certain areas of the BlueBuddies.com site where you have entered such information previously. BlueBuddies.com also collects information about your computer's connection to the Internet. This information allows us to measure traffic on the BlueBuddies.com site and improve the delivery of web pages to you.In addition, third party advertisers or third party advertising servers that place and present advertising on the Service may also collect information from you via cookies, web beacons, clear GIFs or similar technologies. These third party advertisers and advertising servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other uses. The use and collection of your information by these third party advertisers and advertising servers is governed by the relevant third party's privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy. Please note that the privacy policy of these third party advertisers and advertising servers may differ from our privacy policy. You may wish to contact these third party advertisers or third party advertising servers directly if you want more information about their privacy policies or want more information on how to opt-out of the information collection process that some advertisers and advertising servers may use.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
How is this Information Used?
BlueBuddies.com uses the information it collects while you are using the Service in a variety of ways, including the customization of features and advertising that appear on the BlueBuddies.com website. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as advertisers, service providers, and contractors, for a variety of purposes. For example, we may provide our advertisers with information about you and other visitors that will enable our advertisers to better target advertisements to specific visitor classifications.BlueBuddies.com reserves the right to use and to disclose to third parties all of the information that BlueBuddies.com collects online about you and other visitors in any way and for any purpose, with one important exception. BlueBuddies.com will not use the information that it collects online from you while you are using the Service, nor will BlueBuddies.com authorize third parties to use such information, to mail or email promotional offers directly to you unless you have specifically informed BlueBuddies.com that you would like to receive promotional offers from BlueBuddies.com and/or from third parties.Please note that voluntarily provided personal information is available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, through email or web statistics, or in chatrooms – and said information can be viewed, collected and used by others besides BlueBuddies.com. BlueBuddies.com cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information.The BlueBuddies.com website includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third party products or services through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.We also make some content, products and services available through our Service through cooperative relationships with third party providers, where the brands and identifiers of our provider partner appear on the Service in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information provided by you or collected from you in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In certain instances, the provider partner may collect information from you directly. In such cases the privacy policy of the provider partner may apply to the provider partner's use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. You should contact the provider partner directly for more information if you have questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners.BlueBuddies.com may release information about visitors when such release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Service agreement, or to protect the rights, property and/or safety of visitors to our site, the public, or BlueBuddies.com.
The Smurfs will return after these messages:
Children's Privacy Statement
This children's privacy statement details BlueBuddies.com's practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides information regarding certain rights under federal law with respect to said information.This Service is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. If BlueBuddies.com becomes aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we will delete such information from our database. BlueBuddies.com does not knowingly distribute personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen to third parties. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise disseminate personally identifiable contact information through the Service. Because no personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen is collected as part of the Service, we do not abide or condition the participation in the Service's online activities of a child under thirteen on providing personally identifiable information.
How To Make Changes to Your Information
Registered BlueBuddies.com members may update account information at any time by visiting private messages / my profile.
BlueBuddies is the Smurfy Place to Smurf!
WE HAVE MANY MORE PICTURES OF SMURFS THAN JUST THIS!If you're looking for pictures of Smurfs, then what you see above is just the beginning of what we have to offer! BlueBuddies.com has thousands of Smurf pics and thousands of smurfy items of interest. To check out the whole gallery visit our main page - click here!
BLUEBUDDIES SEARCH
Message Board SearchAdvanced SearchHelp / Search Tips
All Smurfs - (Click to Change)Smurf FigurinesSmurf PicturesSmurf Plush
BLUEBUDDIES.COM: THE WORLD'S LARGEST SMURF COMPENDIUM
Copyright © 1995-2020 BlueBuddies.com. Privacy Policy: We respect your privacy. Please read our full privacy statement here. Site usage implies acceptance of our Terms & Conditions. Smurf is copyright Peyo. BlueBuddies.com is a Smurf resource neither sponsored nor endorsed by Peyo or its licensees.   Subscribe to the BlueBuddies RSS Feed.
